realbird.com 2019-04-25

# Privacy Policy for RealBird.com - Members

## This page contains the privacy policy of RealBird Inc. applicable for members

Last modified: May 3, 2018

RealBird (“Company” or “We”) respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy (“Privacy Policy“). This Privacy Policy governs data collection and usage of the products, services, software, platform and websites (collectively, “Services“) provided by the Company. By using the Services, you consent to the data practices described in this policy as well as our Terms of Service. If you do not agree to any part of this Privacy Policy, then you should stop accessing the Services.

This policy applies to information we collect:

  * On the website https://www.RealBird.com (“Site”).
  * In email, text, and other electronic messages between you and this Site.
  * Through mobile and desktop access to this Site and the Services, which provide dedicated non-browser-based interaction between you and this Site.
  * When you interact with our advertising and applications on third-party websites and services, if those applications or advertising include links to this policy.
  * The Services that you may be subscribed to.

This policy does not apply to information collected by:

  * us offline or through any other means, including on any other website operated by Company or any third party; or
  * any third party, including through any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from our Site

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Site and Services. By accessing or using this Site and Services, you agree to this Privacy Policy. This policy may change from time to time (see Changes to Our Privacy Policy). Your continued use of this Site after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates.

## Children Under the Age of 16

Our Site is not intended for children under 16 years of age. No one under age 16 may provide any personal information to or on the Site. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 16. If you are under 16, do not use or provide any information on this Site or on or through any of its features/register on the Site, make any purchases through the Site, use any of the interactive or public comment features of this Site or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, email address, or any screen name or user name you may use. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 16 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 16, please contact us at privacy@realbird.com.

## Information We Collect About You and How We Collect It

We collect several types of information from and about users of our Site and Services, including information:

  * by which you and your business may be personally identified, such as name, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number (“Personal Information“), business name and affiliations, your websites. Company will not delete customer information for paying members. However, Company reserves the right to delete customer information for members with a free account status at any time.
  * that is about you but individually does not identify you;
  * about your internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Site and usage details.

We collect this information:

  * Directly from you when you provide it to us.
  * Automatically as you navigate through the site. Information collected automatically may include usage details, IP addresses, and information collected through cookies, web beacons, and other tracking technologies.
  * From third parties, for example, our business partners, billing services, etc.

## Information You Provide to Us. 

The information we collect on or through our Site may include:

  * Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Site. This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our Site, subscribing to our Services, posting material, or requesting further services. We may also ask you for information when you enter a contest or promotion sponsored by us, and when you report a problem with our Site.
  * Records and copies of your correspondence (including email addresses), if you contact us.
  * Your responses to surveys that we might ask you to complete for research purposes.
  * Details of transactions you carry out through our Site and of the fulfillment of your orders. You may be required to provide financial information before placing an order through our Site.

You also may provide information to be published or displayed (hereinafter, “posted“) on public areas of the Site, or transmitted to other users of the Site or third parties (collectively, “User Contributions“). Your User Contributions are posted on and transmitted to others at your own risk. Please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. Additionally, we cannot control the actions of other users of the Site with whom you may choose to share your User Contributions. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that your User Contributions will not be viewed by unauthorized persons.

## Information We Collect Through Automatic Data Collection Technologies.

As you navigate through and interact with our Site, we may use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions, and patterns, including:

  * Details of your visits to our Site, including traffic data, location data, logs, and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on the Site.
  * Information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system, and browser type.

We also may use these technologies to collect information about your online activities over time and across third-party websites or other online services (behavioral tracking). 

The information we collect automatically is statistical data, but we may maintain it or associate it with personal information we collect in other ways or receive from third parties. It helps us to improve our Site and to deliver a better and more personalized service, including by enabling us to:

  * Estimate our audience size and usage patterns.
  * Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Site according to your individual interests.
  * Speed up your searches.
  * Recognize you when you return to our Site.

The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include:

  * Cookies (or browser cookies). A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Site. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Site.
  * Flash Cookies. Certain features of our Site may use local stored objects (or Flash cookies) to collect and store information about your preferences and navigation to, from, and on our Site. Flash cookies are not managed by the same browser settings as are used for browser cookies. For information about managing your privacy and security settings for Flash cookies, see Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information.
  * Web Beacons. Pages of our the Site and our e-mails may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs, pixel tags, and single-pixel gifs) that permit the Company, for example, to count users who have visited those pages or [opened an email] and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity).

## Third-Party Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies.

Some content or applications, including advertisements, on the Site are served by third-parties, including advertisers, ad networks and servers, content providers, and application providers. These third parties may use cookies alone or in conjunction with web beacons or other tracking technologies to collect information about you when you use our website. The information they collect may be associated with your personal information or they may collect information, including personal information, about your online activities over time and across different websites and other online services. They may use this information to provide you with interest-based (behavioral) advertising or other targeted content.

We do not control these third parties’ tracking technologies or how they may be used. If you have any questions about an advertisement or other targeted content, you should contact the responsible provider directly. For information about how you can opt out of receiving targeted advertising from many providers, see “Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information.”

## How We Use Your Information

We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information:

  * To present our Site and its contents to you.
  * To provide you with information, products, or services that you request from us.
  * To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it.
  * To provide you with notices about your account and subscriptions, including expiration and renewal notices.
  * To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection.
  * To notify you about changes to our Site or any products or services we offer or provide though it.
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features on our Site.
  * In any other way we may describe when you provide the information.
  * For any other purpose with your consent.

We may also use your information to contact you about our own and third-parties goods and services that may be of interest to you. 

We may use the information we have collected from you to enable us to display advertisements to our advertisers’ target audiences. Even though we do not disclose your personal information for these purposes without your consent, if you click on or otherwise interact with an advertisement, the advertiser may assume that you meet its target criteria.

## Disclosure of Your Information

We may disclose aggregated information about our users, and information that does not identify any individual, without restriction.

We may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide as described in this Privacy Policy:

  * To our subsidiaries and affiliates.
  * To contractors, service providers, and other third parties we use to support our business and who are bound by contractual obligations to keep personal information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them.
  * To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of the Company’s assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which personal information held by Company about our Site users is among the assets transferred.
  * To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it.
  * For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.
  * With your consent.

We may also disclose your personal information:

  * To comply with any court order, law, or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.
  * To enforce or apply our Terms of Service https://www.realbird.com/?p=content.terms and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes.
  * If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of the Company, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

## Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information

We strive to provide you with choices regarding the personal information you provide to us. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information:

  * Tracking Technologies and Advertising. You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. To learn how you can manage your Flash cookie settings, visit the Flash player settings page on Adobe’s website. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this site may then be inaccessible or not function properly.
  * Disclosure of Your Information for Third-Party Advertising. If you do not want us to share your personal information with unaffiliated or non-agent third parties for promotional purposes, you can opt-out by sending us an email stating your request to privacy@realbird.com.
  * Promotional Offers from the Company. If you do not wish to have your contact information used by the Company to promote our own or third parties’ products or services, you can opt-out by sending us an email stating your request to privacy@realbird.com. If we have sent you a promotional email, you may send us a return email asking to be omitted from future email distributions. This opt out does not apply to information provided to the Company as a result of a product purchase, warranty registration, product service experience or other transactions.
  * Targeted Advertising. If you do not want us to use information that we collect or that you provide to us to deliver advertisements according to our advertisers’ target-audience preferences, you can opt-out by sending us an email stating your request to privacy@realbird.com

We do not control third parties’ collection or use of your information to serve interest-based advertising. However, these third parties may provide you with ways to choose not to have your information collected or used in this way.

## Accessing and Correcting Your Information

You can review and change your personal information by logging into the Site and visiting your account profile page.

You may also send us an email at support@realbird.com to request access to, correct or delete any personal information that you have provided to us. We cannot delete your personal information except by also deleting your user account. We may not accommodate a request to change information if we believe the change would violate any law or legal requirement or cause the information to be incorrect.

## Compliance with EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) 

The Company provides its Services only to U.S. and Canadian real estate professionals, which are commercial (business) entities. While we agree with the GDPR goals and philosophy to protect consumer data, and voluntarily comply with many of its provisions for our members as well, please be aware that these EU GDPR rules and regulations do not apply to business entities and non-EU citizens/residents.

Our Consumer Privacy Policies are compliant with GDPR regulations and can be reviewed here: http://www.realbird.com/?p=content.consumerprivacy 

## Data Security

We have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration, and disclosure. All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers behind firewalls. Any payment transactions and credit card information will be encrypted using SSL technology and stored only on our PCI compliant payment processors’ sites, by Stripe and Paypal.

The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Site, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone. 

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Site. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Site.

## Changes to Our Privacy Policy

It is our policy to post any changes we make to our Privacy Policy on this page with a notice that the Privacy Policy has been updated on the Site home page. If we make material changes to how we treat our users’ personal information, we will notify you by email to the email address specified in your account. The date the Privacy Policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for ensuring we have an up-to-date active and deliverable email address for you, and for periodically visiting our Site and this Privacy Policy to check for any changes.

## Contact Information

To ask questions or comment about this Privacy Policy and our privacy practices, contact us at:

RealBird Inc.

101 Cooper St, Santa Cruz, CA 95060

Toll free: (866) 551-2934

privacy@realbird.com

In addition, when using certain components of the Site, you will be subject to any additional terms, policies, rules or guidelines applicable to the Site or such components of the Site that may be posted on the Site from time to time, including, without limitation, the Terms of Use located at <https://www.realbird.com/?p=content.terms> and any guidelines applicable to any components of the Site. All such terms are hereby incorporated by reference into this Privacy Policy.
